festhome.com 2018-12-01

# Privacy policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy details how we will treat your personal information under GDPR compliance for all users, based in the EU or anywhere else.

* ### Quick summary:

We recommend reading the entire privacy policy, but here is a quick summary of what we do with your data:

Data Controller: FESTHOME LTD  
---  
All information collected about you on this website is always presently available and may be modified at any time by you within your account. Information created based on your actions (such as submitting to a film festival or watching a film) is also present and clearly shown. You may request that we delete information that we have about you.  
We do not share personal information with third parties for any marketing purposes but we do use third party services to make our services work. These services are GDPR compliant and allow us to make simple functionality such as hosting materials or sending e-mails, or help with support tasks such as the Chat or Support Ticket system.  
We use the collected data for a variety of purposes all within the requested services of our website, such as contacting you, delivering the information to the film festivals you decide to submit to, protecting our service and all clients from frauds, applying filters to your films and settings so that you do not submit a film to a festival where it does not apply, making payments and sending you our newsletters.  
We track you through our website in order to have reliable use data to know what services on our website are being used and how to improve them, or to help our support team when you have a problem.  
We request your consent to do all of this when you create an account, without this account and consent, it is impossible for us to deliver our services. Since we have been GDPR compliant way before it became compulsory, we will not bother you with re-requesting consent.  
* ### What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information ;

  1. information about your computer and your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation);
  2. information related to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;
  3. information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us;
  4. information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters;
  5. any other information that you choose to send to us;
  6. information that you provide to us for the purpose of submitting your materials to us.

* ### Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We may use both "session" cookies and "persistent" cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit.

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiration date.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, that are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.

We may at times or when a support request is created a session replay tool. This tool allows our support team to help view problems and errors the user may be experiencing to guide them to a solution more effectively. All data obtained with this system is solely what is shown on the website and not outside of it, and is only used for support and to enhance the design of the website.

We use third party tools to provide chat and support functionality on the website and may share some PII information, such as e-mail, IP and User ID with them to properly identify you while using these tools.

Our payment services providers may also send you cookies.

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of this and many other websites.

* ### Using your personal information

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

  1. administer the website;
  2. improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
  3. enable your use of the services available on the website;
  4. supply to you services purchased via the website;
  5. send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
  6. send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
  7. send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
  8. send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by email, where you have specifically agreed to this, or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);
  9. provide third parties with statistical information about our users: this information will not be used to identify any individual user;
  10. deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

We will not, without your express consent, provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, PayPal, Stripe and Skrill. We will share information with them only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments.

* ### Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose your personal information:

  1. to the film festivals or other content recipients that you choose to submit your films to, which will become responsible in protecting your data;
  2. to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
  3. in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
  4. in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);
  5. to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling;
  6. to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

* ### International data transfers

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

* ### Security of your personal information

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to the website).

* ### Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are satisfied with any changes.

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

* ### Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to:

  1. the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address).

We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.

You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes by email at any time. In practice, you will expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.

* ### Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

* ### Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you is in need of correction or to be updated.

* ### Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to us by email to help@festhome.com

* ### Data controller

The data controller responsible in respect of the information collected on this website is FESTHOME LTD.
